{
    "subject": "resource/Cratoptera",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Cratoptera",
    "human_readable": "The name of Cratoptera is Cratoptera.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9629830718040466,
            "question": "What is the name of Cratoptera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9214990735054016,
            "question": "Is there a common use for the name Cratoptera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.919477641582489,
            "question": "Is Cratoptera a unique name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791576027870178,
            "question": "What is the origin of the name Cratoptera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8695355653762817,
            "question": "Are there any synonyms for Cratoptera?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.840530276298523,
            "question": "Is Cratoptera a known entity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.835795521736145,
            "question": "Does Cratoptera refer to something specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7503340840339661,
            "question": "Can you find any examples where Cratoptera is used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7383188009262085,
            "question": "What category does Cratoptera belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49542689323425293,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Cratoptera?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Cratoptera is Cratoptera.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2681_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What category does Cratoptera belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2681_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any examples where Cratoptera is used?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2681_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Cratoptera refer to something specific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2681_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2681_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document information provided includes the scientific name \"Cratoptera brunnea Butler, 1881\" which confirms that the genus name for this species is indeed \"Cratoptera\". Therefore, the statement \"The name of Cratoptera is Cratoptera\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}